<resources>
    <string name="ssid">SSID</string>
    <string name="bssid">BSSID</string>
    <string name="link_local_short">LinkLocal</string>
    <string name="link_local_ip">Link Local IP</string>
    <string name="frequency">Frequency</string>
    <string name="channel">Channel</string>
    <string name="link_speed">Link Speed</string>
    <string name="gateway">Gateway</string>
    <string name="dns">DNS</string>
    <string name="dhcp">DHCP</string>

    <string name="show_prefix_length">Show prefix length(s)</string>

    <string name="ssid_description">Service Set Identifier. Your networks name.</string>
    <string name="bssid_description">Basic Service Set Identifier. A 48-bit label abiding by MAC-48 conventions which identifies your devices basic service set.</string>
    <string name="frequency_description">The radio frequency band employed for WiFi signal transmission, following the IEEE 802.11 technical standards. Bands for use in WiFi communication provided by IEEE 802.11 lie at 900 MHz, 2.4 GHz, 3.6 GHz, 4.9 GHz, 5 GHz, 5.9 GHz, 6 GHz and 60 GHz. Bands are divided into several distinct channels.</string>
    <string name="channel_description">The sub frequencies which the main frequency bands are divided into, and via which WiFi communication takes place. As per the IEEE 802.11 standard, channels are numbered at 5 MHz spacing within a band (except in the 60 GHz band, where they are 2.16 GHz apart), where the number corresponds to the center frequency of the channel. Although channels are numbered at 5 MHz spacing, transmitters generally occupy at least 20 MHz, and standards allow for channels to be bonded together to form wider channels for faster throughput.</string>
    <string name="link_speed_description">The theoretical data transmission max speed between your device and the router.</string>
    <string name="rssi_description">Received Signal Strength Indicator. A measurement of the power level of the received signal expressed in decibels (dBm). The dBm value indicates the received power level relative to 1 milliwatt (mW). Higher dBm values signify stronger signals, while lower values indicate weaker ones.</string>
    <string name="gateway_description">A Gateway is a device uniting the functionality of a modem, i.e., communicating with your ISP (Internet Service Provider), and a router, i.e., translating the data received by the modem and distributing it as WiFi signal to the client devices being present in the network.</string>
    <string name="dns_description">Domain Name System. Associates domain names with various types of information, acting as a database. Most notably, it translates domain names to their underlying IP addresses, needed for locating and communicating with them.</string>
    <string name="dhcp_description">Dynamic Host Configuration Protocol. A service which automatically assigns IP addresses and other network parameters to devices connected to a network.</string>
    <string name="disabled">Disabled</string>
    <string name="disconnected">Disconnected</string>
    <string name="connected">Connected</string>

    <string name="loopback">Loopback</string>
    <string name="site_local_ip">Site Local IP</string>
    <string name="site_local_short">SiteLocal</string>
    <string name="ula">ULA</string>
    <string name="gua">GUA</string>
    <string name="public_ip">Public IP</string>
    <string name="public_">Public</string>
    <string name="multicast_ip">Multicast IP</string>

    <string name="ipv4">IPv4</string>
    <string name="ipv6">IPv6</string>
    <string name="refresh_button">Refresh button</string>
    <string name="open_wifi_settings_button">Open WiFi settings button</string>
    <string name="open_widget_settings_button">Open widget settings button</string>

    <string name="refresh_periodically">Refresh periodically</string>
    <string name="refresh_on_low_battery">Refresh on low battery</string>
    <string name="display_last_refresh_time">Last refresh time display</string>

    <string name="loopback_description">A loopback IP address, commonly represented as 127.0.0.1 in IPv4, is a reserved address that allows a device to communicate with itself. When data is sent to the loopback address, it is internally routed back to the same device, enabling local testing of networking functionality. This address, often referred to as "localhost", is widely used for diagnostic and development purposes to ensure the proper functioning of network-related components on a device without the need for external connections. In IPv6, the loopback address is typically represented as ::1.</string>
    <string name="unique_local_description">Unique Local Addresses (ULAs) in IPv6 are a reserved set of addresses designed for local communication within an organization or site. Introduced as the successor to site-local addresses, as per RFC 4193, ULAs enable devices within a specific network to communicate locally without the need for global uniqueness. They serve as a practical solution for private, internal use in IPv6 networks, ensuring local connectivity while addressing the limitations of the deprecated site-local addressing concept.</string>
    <string name="link_local_description">Link-local addresses are a type of address assigned to network interfaces for communication within the scope of a single network link. In IPv6, link-local addresses are automatically configured with the address range starting with FE80::, facilitating communication on the local network segment. In IPv4, link-local addresses fall within the range of 169.254.0.1 to 169.254.255.254 and are commonly used in scenarios where a DHCP server is unavailable, allowing devices on the same network link to communicate locally.</string>
    <string name="multicast_description">Multicast addresses are a type of IP address used for communication between multiple hosts that belong to a specific group. In IPv4, multicast addresses range from 224.0.0.0 to 239.255.255.255. Devices interested in receiving multicast traffic join a specific multicast group identified by one of these addresses. In IPv6, multicast addresses are similarly used, and they start with the prefix FF00::, providing an efficient way for multiple devices to share information selectively across networks. Multicast addresses enable applications such as video streaming, online gaming, and other scenarios where content is meant for a defined group of recipients rather than all devices on a network.</string>
    <string name="public_description">Public IP addresses are unique addresses assigned to devices on the internet, allowing them to be identified and communicate with other devices across the global network. These addresses are globally routable and are registered with regional internet registries (RIRs) to ensure uniqueness. In both IPv4 and IPv6, public IP addresses are distinct from private addresses and are used for direct communication between devices on the internet.\n\nWiFi Widget retrieves the public addresses via www.ipify.org. Considering their uniqueness, you should be extra mindful about sharing them.</string>
    <string name="global_unicast_description">Global unicast addresses are a specific category of IP addresses used for communication across the entire internet. In IPv6, global unicast addresses are part of the global unicast address space and are routable on the global internet. These addresses typically start with the prefix 2000::/3.\n\nGlobal unicast addresses play a crucial role in providing unique and globally reachable identifiers for devices connected to the internet. Unlike link-local or site-local addresses that have limited scope, global unicast addresses allow devices to communicate globally, enabling the seamless exchange of information across different networks and regions.</string>
    <string name="site_local_description">Site-local addresses were part of both IPv4 and IPv6 address spaces, designated for communication within specific sites or organizations. In IPv4, these addresses fell within the private address ranges defined by RFC 1918 (10.0.0.0 to 10.255.255.255, 172.16.0.0 to 172.31.255.255, and 192.168.0.0 to 192.168.255.255), while in IPv6, site-local addresses were initially designated with the fec0::/10 prefix. However, due to issues with site-local addresses, IPv6 transitioned to using Unique Local Addresses (ULAs) as their successor. In both IPv4 and IPv6, site-local (or equivalent) addresses were reserved for local communication within designated networks and were not intended for global Internet routing.</string>
    <string name="unique_local_ip">Unique Local IP</string>
    <string name="global_unicast_ip">Global Unicast IP</string>
    <string name="mc">MC</string>
    <string name="background">Background</string>
    <string name="primary">Primary</string>
    <string name="secondary">Secondary</string>
    <string name="preset">Preset</string>
    <string name="custom">Custom</string>
    <string name="loopback_ip">Loopback IP</string>
    <string name="rssi">RSSI</string>
    <string name="standard">Standard</string>
    <string name="standard_description">The IEEE 802.11 WiFi standard defines protocols for wireless communication networks. It specifies how devices like computers and routers communicate over the airwaves, including aspects like frequency bands, data rates, and security protocols. </string>
    <string name="very_small">Very Small</string>
    <string name="small">Small</string>
    <string name="medium">Medium</string>
    <string name="large">Large</string>
    <string name="very_large">Very Large</string>
    <string name="generation">Generation</string>
    <string name="generation_description">Another nomenclature for the WiFi standards.</string>
    <string name="security">Security</string>
    <string name="security_description">The used security protocol.</string>
    <string name="signal_strength">Signal Strength</string>
    <string name="signal_strength_description">The signal strength level based on the RSSI. The used mapping function is:
    \n\t\tExcellent: Up to -60 dBm
    \n\t\tGood: -61 to -70 dBm
    \n\t\tFair: -71 to -80 dBm
    \n\t\tWeak: -81 to -90 dBm
    \n\t\tPoor: -91 dBm and below</string>
</resources>