<resources>
    <string-array name="ssid">
        <item>Service Set Identifier. Your network\'s name.</item>
        <item>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Service_set_(802.11_network)#SSID</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="ip">
        <item>Internet Protocol Address, serving the two main purposes of identifying the network interface of your device and providing it\'s location within the network, thereby making it addressable. WiFi Widget displays the IPv4 representation, which corresponds to a 32-bit number, as opposed to the IPv6 format, which corresponds to a 128-bit number. The displayed address is your internal one, meaning that it\'s merely visible from within your network.</item>
        <item>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/IP_address</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="frequency">
        <item>The radio frequency band employed for WiFi signal transmission, following the IEEE 802.11 technical standards. Bands for use in WiFi communication provided by IEEE 802.11 lie at 900 MHz, 2.4 GHz, 3.6 GHz, 4.9 GHz, 5 GHz, 5.9 GHz, 6 GHz and 60 GHz. Bands are divided into several distinct channels.</item>
        <item>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/List_of_WLAN_channels</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="channel">
        <item>The sub frequencies which the main frequency bands are divided into, and via which WiFi communication takes place. As per the IEEE 802.11 standard, channels are numbered at 5 MHz spacing within a band (except in the 60 GHz band, where they are 2.16 GHz apart), where the number corresponds to the centre frequency of the channel. Although channels are numbered at 5 MHz spacing, transmitters generally occupy at least 20 MHz, and standards allow for channels to be bonded together to form wider channels for faster throughput.</item>
        <item>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/List_of_WLAN_channels</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="linkspeed">
        <item>The theoretical data transmission max speed between your device and the router.</item>
        <item />
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="gateway">
        <item>A Gateway is a device uniting the functionality of a modem, i.e., communicating with your ISP (Internet Service Provider), and a router, i.e., translating the data received by the modem and distributing it as WiFi signal to the client devices being present in the network.</item>
        <item>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Gateway_(telecommunications)#Network_gateway</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="dns">
        <item>Domain Name System. Associates domain names with various types of information, acting as a database. Most notably, it translates domain names to their underlying IP addresses, needed for locating and communicating with them.</item>
        <item>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Domain_Name_System</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="dhcp">
        <item>Dynamic Host Configuration Protocol. A service which automatically assigns IP addresses and other network parameters to devices connected to a network.</item>
        <item>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Dynamic_Host_Configuration_Protocol</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="netmask">
        <item>Also referred to as subnet mask. A bitmask determining the subnetwork within which the DHCP may operate.</item>
        <item>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Subnetwork</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>
